[{"answer": " Hey, Rosa.  Hows it going", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " Hi, Katie.  Things are going great.  How about you", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 12, "question": " Hey, Rosa.  Hows it going", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Pretty good.  Ive been thinking about our trip all week", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Hi, Katie.  Things are going great.  How about you", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Me too.  Im excited about it already", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Pretty good.  Ive been thinking about our trip all week", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " I think planning it is going to be really fun", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Me too.  Im excited about it already", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " It is.  We have a lot to do though, I think", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 16, "question": " I think planning it is going to be really fun", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Yes, but you know me.  Im the spontaneous one.  I could hop on the plane t", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 17, "question": " It is.  We have a lot to do though, I think", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Not me.  That would scare me to death.  I like to plan", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Yes, but you know me.  Im the spontaneous one.  I could hop on the plane t", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " I know.  I knew you would want to.  You probably have a list of things we need t", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Not me.  That would scare me to death.  I like to plan", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Actually, I do", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 26, "question": " I know.  I knew you would want to.  You probably have a list of things we need t", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " OK.  Whats first", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Actually, I do", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Well, the first thing I think we need to do is book our tickets.  Is June 6th  Jun", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 31, "question": " OK.  Whats first", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Sure, those dates still work for me", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Well, the first thing I think we need to do is book our tickets.  Is June 6th  Jun", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " All right.  I think we can both work on the flights.  Lets each look online for th", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Sure, those dates still work for me", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": "", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 37, "question": " All right.  I think we can both work on the flights.  Lets each look online for th", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " OK.  Why dont I look at the first five sites and you check out the last five", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 40, "question": "", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " OK.  Lets do that and well talk about what we find next week.  The second thin", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 41, "question": " OK.  Why dont I look at the first five sites and you check out the last five", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Dont you want to just wait until we get there to find something", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 45, "question": " OK.  Lets do that and well talk about what we find next week.  The second thin", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " No, summer is a busy travel time.  All of the hotels might be full if we wait unti", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Dont you want to just wait until we get there to find something", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " I guess youre right", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 50, "question": " No, summer is a busy travel time.  All of the hotels might be full if we wait unti", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " I brought two travel guides with me today about Ireland.  Here, have a look", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 51, "question": " I guess youre right", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Great", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 55, "question": " I brought two travel guides with me today about Ireland.  Here, have a look", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Why dont we each take one, read through the hotel sections, and highlight tw", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Great", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Sure.  That seems like a good way to find one", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Why dont we each take one, read through the hotel sections, and highlight tw", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Now, we also need to have an idea of what we want to do in Dublin and mayb", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Sure.  That seems like a good way to find one", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Wow!  You really want to plan everything", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Now, we also need to have an idea of what we want to do in Dublin and mayb", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Well, we dont want to get there and waste time trying to figure everything out a", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Wow!  You really want to plan everything", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " I know.  Im just kidding", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Well, we dont want to get there and waste time trying to figure everything out a", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " These books also have sections on attractions, things to do, and restaurants", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 74, "question": " I know.  Im just kidding", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " OK.  What about restaurants", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 78, "question": " These books also have sections on attractions, things to do, and restaurants", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Why dont we just put a little star in the book next the restaurants that soun", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 79, "question": " OK.  What about restaurants", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Why dont we just put a little star in the book next the restaurants that soun", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " So, we have flights, hotel, things to do, and places to eat.  That is on our list o", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 84, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Sure.  How about Wednesday", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 89, "question": " So, we have flights, hotel, things to do, and places to eat.  That is on our list o", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " That works", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Sure.  How about Wednesday", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Thanks for bringing the books and your planning list", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 91, "question": " That works", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Youre welcome", "docId": "09-02", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Thanks for bringing the books and your planning list", "qSentId": 91}]
